https://www.akronbrass.com/customer-support-privacy/

Cookie Policy
This site uses and sets "cookies" on your computer to help make this website better.
We use cookies to remember log-in details and provide secure log-in, collect statistics to optimize site functionality, and deliver content tailored to your interests. Click accept to give your consent to accept cookies and go directly to the site or click on more information to see detailed descriptions of the types of cookies we store.
Click here to learn about cookie settings.
Accept
Decline
My Account Log In
Distributor Locator
Support
Contact Us
Order Forms
Repair
Careers
Your Language:
English
Chinese
German
Russian
Spanish
Your Language:
Akron Brass Chinese
Akron Brass
Call Now
+1 (800) 228-1161
0
You have no items in your cart.
My Quote (0)
You have no items in your quote.
You have no items in your cart.
All Categories
All Categories
Fire Hose Nozzles
Firefighting Monitors
Firefighting Valves & Wyes
LED Emergency Vehicle Lights & Scene Lighting
Emergency Vehicle Electronics for Firefighter Safety
Fire Truck Cord Reels and More
Monitors
View portable monitors.
Mercury Quick Attack LE
Valves
Revolution Intake Valve
Wye
Valve Service Kits
Scene Lighting
Revel Scout
SAME-DAY SHIPPING
Buy direct for speedy delivery. Same-Day Shipping by 3:30 PM EST, M-F.
BUY NOW
Select items for direct purchase from Akron Brass. US Shipping only.
DEDICATED SERVICE
Consult our experts for product details and technical assistance
Find a Dealer
Privacy Policy
We Are Committed to Your Right to Privacy
Akron Brass Company (“Akron Brass”)  respects your right to privacy. We developed this Privacy Statement to inform you about our practices. Questions regarding this Privacy Statement should be directed to kmorrow@idexcorp.com.Privacy is a concern to most Internet users. Akron Brass is acutely aware of, and sensitive to, the privacy concerns of our customers. We assure you that we do not collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us. If you are registering to use the site you will be asked to provide certain information. We are asking for this information solely for the purpose of providing the services offered and authenticating your identity when you login.Privacy Policy EnforcementIf you feel that Akron Brass is violating this Privacy Statement, please contact us at kmorrow@idexcorp.com.Use of Postal & Email AddressesWe occasionally make the names, postal addresses, and email addresses of our customers available to highly screened companies that offer products and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive these third-party offers, please let us know by contacting Akron Brass at 1-800-228-1161.Traffic DataWe collect click-stream data such as referring URL, browser and platform, time of visit, pages visited and searches performed. These statistics are used to help us improve the performance of our website and better serve our customers. We analyze this data to establish trends and help us improve your online experience. Aggregated traffic data may be shared with potential advertisers, research firms, and business partners for demographic purposes. When used in this aggregated form no one will be able to identify or contact you.Use of E-mail AddressesWhen you register on akronbrass.com, you may receive email promotions from time to time. To unsubscribe from these emails, follow the unsubscribe directions contained in the email so that you may opt-out of future e-mails. E-mails that confirm business transactions will always be sent to you.Use of CookiesA "cookie" is a text file that our website sends to your browser to store your preferences. Cookies allow our website to "remember" information about your preferences either until you exit your current browser window (if the cookie is temporary) or until you disable or delete the cookie. Many users prefer to use cookies to help them navigate a website as seamlessly as possible. We use "cookies" to enhance your experience on our site. You should be aware that cookies contain no more information than you volunteer, and they are not able to "invade" your hard drive and return to the sender with personal or other information from your computer. If you choose not to accept a cookie, you are still welcome at our website; however we will not be able to accept online orders.Sending You Responses and UpdatesWe generally respond to any e-mail questions, requests for service or information, and other inquiries we receive. We may also retain this correspondence to improve our products, services and website. Frequently we retain contact information so that we can send individuals updates or other important information about our services and products.SurveysFrom time-to-time we may request information via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you always have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Survey information will be used to monitor or improve this website, and to improve our customer service and product offerings.Terms of UseThe Akron Brass website may contain links to third-party sites. The linked sites are not under the control of Akron Brass, and Akron Brass is not responsible for the contents of any linked site, any link contained in a linked site, any changes or updates to such linked sites, or any transmission from any linked site. Akron Brass is providing these links to third-party sites only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Akron Brass of the site.License and Site AccessAkron Brass grants you a limited license to access and make personal use of this site and not to download (other than page caching) or modify it, or any portion of it, except with express written consent of Akron Brass. This license does not include any resale or commercial use of this site or its contents; any collection and use of any product listings, descriptions, or prices; any derivative use of this site or its contents; any downloading or copying of account information for the benefit of another merchant; or any use of data mining, robots, or similar data gathering and extraction tools. This site or any portion of this site may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without express written consent of Akron Brass. You are granted a limited, revocable, and nonexclusive right to create a hyperlink to the home page of akronbrass.com so long as the link does not portray Akron Brass, its parent company, or their products or services in a false, misleading, derogatory, or otherwise offensive matter. You may not use any Akron Brass logo or other proprietary graphic or trademark as part of the link without express written permission.CopyrightThe site and the content within the site are the property of Akron Brass or its affiliates and are protected by United States copyright laws and international treaty provisions. The compilation, organization and display of the content as well as all software and inventions used on and in connection with this Site are the exclusive property of Akron Brass. These materials may not be copied or redistributed for any for any purposes without prior written permission from Akron Brass.Trademark InformationAKROMATIC, AKRON, AKRON BRASS, BLACK WIDOW, PYROLITE, TORK-LOK, TURBOJET, YOUR CHOICE BEHIND THE LINE OF FIRE, AKRON BRASS LOGO, EXTENDA-LITE QUARTZ FLOOD LIGHTING, and FIRECRAFT™ are registered trademarks of Akron Brass Company. All other registered and/or unregistered trademarks displayed on this site constitute the intellectual property of their respective holders.
x
Add to Cart
Price:
Actual Price:
Our price is lower than the manufacturer's "minimum advertised price."
As a result, we cannot show you the price in catalog or the product page.
You have no obligation to purchase the product once you know the price. You can simply remove the item from your cart.
Our price is lower than the manufacturer's "minimum advertised price."
As a result, we cannot show you the price in catalog or the product page.
You have no obligation to purchase the product once you know the price. You can simply remove the item from your cart.
Returns (RMA)
Warranty
Order Forms
Resource Center
REQUEST PRODUCT DEMO
Contact us for a hands-on demonstration.
FIND A DISTRIBUTOR
Learn where to buy.
CUSTOM SOLUTIONS
Contact an engineer for a solution customized to your needs.
RESOURCE CENTER
Get access to useful guides and reference material to help you get the most out of your Akron Brass products.
Akron Brass Firefighting Equipment
Fire Nozzles, Firefighting Valves and More
As a global manufacturer of fire fighting equipment and more, Akron Brass designs and manufactures products that meet
the demands of the industry and help you perform your job safely and efficiently. Whether you need fire nozzles,
fire fighting valves, monitors or the latest technology in vehicle electronics, Akron Brass has a large selection
to meet your unique application. Our fire fighting equipment is safe and effective for your emergency situation.
Contact Info
Address
Akron Brass Company | 343 Venture Blvd
|Wooster, Ohio 44691
Weldon, a Division of Akron Brass | 3656 Paragon Drive | Columbus, OH 43228 |weldoninc.com
Akron Brass, Ocala location | 607 NW 27th Ave |Ocala, FL 34475
Select Store:
© 2019 Akron Brass Company is an ISO 9001:2015 Registered Company from Eagle Registrations.
This achievement attests to our commitment of servicing our customers.
343 Venture Blvd, Wooster, OH 44691 (Additional Locations) | 1-800-228-1161
*Email Address
*Password
Register
Forgot?
Login
Close Window
Continue shopping
Back to top
